Everybody! Central Perk
is proud to present...
...the music of Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks.
I wanna start with a song
that's about that moment...
...when you suddenly realize
what life is really all about.
Okay, here we go.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Oh, great. This is just
The One With The Blackout
This is so cool, you guys.
The entire city's blacked out.
It's all of Manhattan.
They have no idea...
...when it's back on.
-You guys, this is big.
-Pants and a sweater. Why, Mom?
Who will I meet in a blackout?
Power-company guys?
Eligible looters?
-Can we talk about this later? Okay.
-Can I borrow the phone?
I wanna call my apartment
and check on my grandma.
What's my number?
I never call me.
Oh, my God! It's her.
It's that Victoria 's Secret model.
Something Goodacre.
Hi, Mom, it's Jill.
She 's right. It's Jill.
Jill Goodacre. Oh, my God!
I am trapped in an A TM vestibule
with Jill Goodacre.
Is it a vestibule?
Maybe it's an atrium.
Yeah, that is the part
to focus on, you idiot.
I' m fine. I' m just stuck
at the bank in an ATM vestibule.
Jill says vestibule,
I'm going with vestibule.
I' m fine. No, l' m not alone.
I don't know, some guy.
Oh, some guy. I am some guy.
Jill, I saw you with some guy
last night.
Yes, he was some guy.
Hey, everyone.
Officiating at tonight's blackout
is Rabbi T ribbiani.
Chandler's old roommate was Jewish.
These are our only candles.
So happy Hanukkah!
Look! Ugly Naked Guy
lit a bunch of candles.
That had to hurt!
All right, all right!
It's been 14 1/2 minutes...
...and you still haven 't said
one word. God!
Do something!
Just make contact. Smile!
There you go.
You 're definitely scaring her.
Hello? Oh, hi, Mom.
Mom.
Mom, you' re tripping!
Dexter's a dog.
The blackout's scaring him.
You'd pee in Dad's shoes too
if you didn't know.
All right, call me back.
-Mothers.
-Yeah.
Attaboy! A word.
That wasn 't so hard.
Mothers. Yeah!
Mothers. Yeah! Perfect.
Don 't smile.
Would you like to call somebody?
Yeah, about 300 guys I went
to high school with.
Yeah, thanks.
-Hello?
-It's me.
-It's Chandler. Are you okay?
-Yeah, l' m fine.
I' m stuck in an ATM vestibule...
...with Jill Goodacre.
-What?
-l' m stuck...
...in an ATM vestibule...
...with Jill Goodacre.
I have no idea what you said.
Put Joey on the phone.
-What's up, man?
-l' m stuck...
...in an ATM vestibule...
...with Jill Goodacre!
Oh, my God!
He's trapped in an ATM vestibule
with Jill Goodacre!
Chandler, listen.
Like that thought
never entered my mind.
-Okay.
-Somebody.
-I'll go. I'll go.
-Okay.
Senior year of college,
on a pool table.
-Pool table?
-That's my sister.
Okay, my weirdest place
would have to be...
...the women's room of the New York
City Public Library.
Oh, my God! What were you
doing in a library?
-Pheebs, what about you?
-Oh, Milwaukee.
It's a really weird place.
Ross?
Disneyland, 1 989.
" It's a small world after all. "
No way.
The ride broke down...
...so Carol and I went behind
those mechanical Dutch children.
We were asked never to return
to the Magic Kingdom.
Let's see, that leaves....
-Rachel?
-Come on, I already went.
-You did not go.
-I did.
T ell us. Come on.
All right, the weirdest place
would have to be...
...the foot of the bed.
-Step back!
-We have a winner!
This must be what the fridge
looks like with the door closed.
Spooky.
Anybody hungry?
We got a Klondike...soup.
I've never had a relationship
with that kind of passion.
Where you have to have somebody
even in a theme park.
It was the only thing to do
that didn't have a line.
Barry wouldn't even kiss me
on a miniature golf course.
-Come on.
-No.
He said we held up
the people behind us.
You didn't marry him because...?
Do you think there are people
that go through life...
... never having that kind of...?
-Probably.
-Really?
I'll tell you something.
Passion is way overrated.
-Yeah, right.
-lt is.
Eventually, it kind of burns out.
But hopefully what you're left
with is trust and security and....
In my ex-wife's case,
lesbianism.
For those people who miss out
on that passion thing...
...there's other stuff.
-Okay.
-But I don't think that'll be you.
-You don't?
-See, I see...
-... big passion in your future.
-Really?
-You do?
-I do.
Ross, you' re so great.
It's never gonna happen.
-What?
-You and Rachel.
What? Me and Ra?
Why not?
You waited too long
to make your move...
...and now you' re
in the "friend zone. "
-l' m not in the zone.
-No, Ross. You' re mayor of the zone.
Look, l' m taking my time, all right?
I' m laying the groundwork.
Every day I get
a little bit closer to
Priesthood!
I'm telling you, she has
no idea what you're thinking.
She just ran her fingers
through my hair.
-Were you missing that interaction?
-No, no, no.
This is running fingers
through your hair, okay?
Now this is a tousle.
If you don't ask her out soon,
you'll be in the zone forever.
I will, I will.
I'm waiting for the right moment.
What?
-What, now?
-Yeah.
What's messing you up?
The wine? The moonlight?
You gotta go up to her and say,
" Look, Rachel, l"
-What?
-We' re shushing...
... because we' re trying
to hear something.
-What? What?
-Don't you hear that?
See?
-Would you like gum?
-ls it sugarless?
-Sorry, it's not.
-Then no, thanks.
What was that?
Mental note: If Jill Goodacre
offers you gum, you take it.
If she offers you mangled
animal carcass, you take it!
New York City has no power
And the milk is getting sour
But to me it is not scary
Because I stay away from dairy
-Here goes.
-You'll do it?
-I'll do it.
-Want help?
You come out, you' re a dead man.
-Good luck, man.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
Where you going?
You can't go out there.
-Why not?
-Because of the reason.
-That would be?
-I can't tell you.
Joey, what's going on?
You gotta promise you'll
never tell Ross that I told you.
-What?
-He's planning your birthday party.
-Oh, my God! I love him!
-You better act surprised.
-About what?
-My surprise party.
-What surprise party?
-Oh, stop it. Joey already told me.
He didn't tell me.
Don't look at me. This is Ross' thing.
This is typical.
I'm always the last to know.
You are not. We tell you stuff.
I was the last one to know when
Chandler got bit by the peacock.
I was the last to know
you had a crush on Joey.
What?
Looks like I was second to last.
You had a crush on me?
All right. It wasn't a crush,
it was a dent.
Big dent?
You were moving your furniture.
I thought you had nice arms.
Nice arms, huh?
Hey, Mon, l' m moving the chair.
Do anything for you?
With all the lights out
you can actually see the stars.
It's so nice.
I have a question.
Actually, it's not
so much a question.
It's more
of a general wondering....
ment.
-Okay.
-Okay. Here it goes.
Well, for a while now,
I've been wanting to....
-Yes, that's right.
-Look at that little kitty!
What?
Top of the world
Looking down on creation
And the only explanation I can find
Is the love that I found
Ever since you 've been around
All right, this is just Bactine.
It won't hurt.
-Ow!
-Sorry, that was wax.
Poor little T ooty's scared.
We should find his owner.
Why not put poor T ooty in the hall?
During a blackout?
She'll get trampled.
Yeah?
Damage control. Get back to the gum.
Gum would be perfection.
Gum would be perfection?
Could've said,
"Gum would be nice. " But, no.
For me, gum is perfection.
I loathe myself!
Oh, no, they' re nuns.
They hate all living things.
Hi. We just found this cat,
and we' re looking for the owner.
Yeah, it's mine.
-He seems to hate you. Are you sure?
-It's my cat. Give me my cat.
-Wait a minute. What's his name?
-Bob Buttons.
-Bob Buttons?
-Bob Buttons. Here, Bob Buttons.
You are a very bad man!
You owe me a cat.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Where did you go, little kitty?
IKitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here, kitty, kitty.
-Hi.
-Buona sera.
Wow!
Mon, wanna go for a ride
in my racecar?
I'll bring my arms.
We can bring my wheelbarrow
for your teeth!
Come on, lucky sixes!
Everybody, this is Paolo.
Paolo, I want you to meet my friends.
This is Monica...
-Hi.
-...and Joey...
-...and Ross.
Hi.
He doesn't speak much English.
Monopoly!
Look at that!
So, where did Paolo come from?
Italy, I think.
No, I mean tonight.
Suddenly, into our lives.
That cat turned out to be Paolo's cat.
Isn't that funny?
That is funny.
And Rachel keeps touching him.
I looked all over and couldn't find
the kitty anywhere.
I found him. It was Paolo's cat.
Well, there you go.
Last to know again.
And I'm guessing, this is Paolo?
Paolo, this is Phoebe.
You betcha!
All right. Okay. What next?
Blow a bubble. A bubble's good.
It's got a boyish charm. It's impish.
Here we go.
Nice going, imp!
It's okay. All I need to do...
...is reach over and put it
back in my mouth.
Good save!
We 're back on track and I'm...
... chewing someone else 's gum.
This is not my gum!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
And now you 're choking.
You all right?
My God! You' re choking!
-Better?
-Yes.
Thank you. That was....
-That was....
-Perfection?
That was no tousle.
-What'd he say that was so funny?
-I have absolutely no idea.
That's classic.
My God, you guys! What am I doing?
This is so un-me!
If you want, I'll do it.
I just wanna bite his bottom lip.
But I won't.
The first time he smiled at me...
...those seconds were more exciting
than weeks with Barry.
Did you rent mopeds?
Because I've heard
Oh, it's not about that right now.
I know it's superficial,
and we have nothing in common...
...and we don't even speak
the same language, but, God!
-Paolo, hi.
-Ross.
Listen....
Listen, something you should know.
Rachel and I are....
We' re kind of a thing.
-Thing?
-Thing. Yes, thing.
-You have the sex?
-No.
No, technically the sex
is not being had. But that's....
But that's not the point.
The point is that
Rachel and I should be....
Well, Rachel and l
should be together.
And if you get in the
-ln bed
-No.
No, not where I was going.
If you get in the way of us
becoming a thing...
...then I would be, well, very sad.
So, do you...?
-So you do know a little English?
-Little.
-Do you know the word "crap-weasel "?
-No.
That's funny.
You are a huge crap-weasel.
We've been doing this
for an hour. It's easy.
Ready?
Okay? Now try it.
You gotta whip it.
Look, look. The last candle's
about to burn out.
T en, nine, eight, seven...
... minus 46, minus 47,
minus 48....
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
IKind of spooky without any lights.
Okay, guys, I have the definitive one.
This probably isn't the best time
to bring it up...
...but you have to throw
a party for Monica.
-This has been fun.
-Yes.
Thanks for letting me
use your phone...
...and for saving my life.
Well, goodbye, Chandler.
I had a great blackout.
See you.
Hi, l' m account number 71 43457.
I don't know if you got that...
... but I would really
like a copy of the tape.